<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Hello, Siddhesh Kanawade here</title>
    <link>https://siddheshkanawade.github.io/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Hello, Siddhesh Kanawade here</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 21:20:22 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://siddheshkanawade.github.io/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CS 301: Operating Systems: Assignment 2</title>
      <link>https://siddheshkanawade.github.io/blogs/pintos_assign2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2022 21:20:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siddheshkanawade.github.io/blogs/pintos_assign2/</guid>
      <description>Group Members Siddhesh Kanawade: siddhesh.kanawade@iitgn.ac.in Kushgra Jain: kushagra.jain@iitgn.ac.in Utkarsh Mishra: utkarsh.mishra@iitgn.ac.in
Preliminaries The code is highly self explanatory due to multiple comments and humanly readable variables and function names. The main goal of this assignment was to understand the Userprog in the Pintos Operating System. Also, please note that, the comments in the datastructure section are drafted to act as the description of the struct, enum, or data type.
ARGUMENT PASSING &amp;mdash;- DATA STRUCTURES &amp;mdash;- The present data structures sufficed the requirement of this task and hence no new datastructures were created.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CS 301: Operating Systems: Assignment 1</title>
      <link>https://siddheshkanawade.github.io/blogs/pintos_assign1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 23:38:03 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siddheshkanawade.github.io/blogs/pintos_assign1/</guid>
      <description>Group Members Siddhesh Kanawade: siddhesh.kanawade@iitgn.ac.in Kushgra Jain: kushagra.jain@iitgn.ac.in Utkarsh Mishra: utkarsh.mishra@iitgn.ac.in
Preliminaries The code is highly self explanatory due to multiple comments and humanly readable variables and function names. The main goal of this assignment was to understand the Threads in the Pintos Operating System. Also, please note that, the comments in the datastructure section are drafted to act as the description of the struct, enum, or data type.
Alarm Clock Data Structures In thread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geoclassifier-Granule.ai</title>
      <link>https://siddheshkanawade.github.io/blogs/geoclassifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 02:10:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://siddheshkanawade.github.io/blogs/geoclassifier/</guid>
      <description>Brief Overview of Problem Statement The goal of this challenge is to classify a given geographical feature into one of the six classes.
&amp;lsquo;Demolition&amp;rsquo;: 0 &amp;lsquo;Road&amp;rsquo;: 1 &amp;lsquo;Residential&amp;rsquo;: 2 &amp;lsquo;Commercial&amp;rsquo;: 3 &amp;lsquo;Industrial&amp;rsquo;: 4 &amp;lsquo;Mega Projects&amp;rsquo;: 5 Dataset Analysis The dataset consisted of training and test data. Both the datasets were in .geojson format. The problem statement requires to use CVPR EarthVision dataset. The entire description of the dataset and usage of different Deep Learning technics to produce it can be found on the attached link.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
